Today I have to
up by donating
blood with
ulcerative
colitis.
Hello, I'm your
not so typical
chronically ill
chick who
doesn't think
before she does
stuff at the
worst times.
I have
ulcerative
colitis, I'm on
other fun party
favors, and I
literally had
ulcer so bad
that when I
went in to have
them
cauterized, I
woke up in
quarantine
because the
specialist had
never seen
ulcer so bad
without see
death being
involved.
It thankfully
had nothing to
do with see
death and I was
started on
foreign fusions
of powerful
medication. So,
after the first
infusion, I
start feeling
better, good,
right?
Now, I work at
a church. A
good one that's
pro LGBT and
actually has
charities to
help the
community.
One of our
charities is a
partnership
with the Red
Cross where we
hold blood
drives every
two months.
This charity
project is one
of my
responsibilities.
We normally
have a pretty
good turnout
and the
Red Cross says
we're one of
their best
drives. But
this time
around, our
numbers were
low, and some
of
our regular
donors got
deferred for
low hemoglobin.
So, I decided
that, since my
insights aren't
hemorrhaging
anymore, I'll
donate a pint
to help out.
So, I go over
and get hooked
up and give
my donation. I
get off the
table feeling
okay and I'm
immediately
called over to
the
registration
desk because
the church
volunteers need
some supplies.
So, I head off
to get them.
Suddenly,
I feel
lightheaded and
I'm floating
sideways. Then,
I just remember
waking up
laughing at the
realization I
passed out. I'm
on the floor,
and my
volunteers who
are mostly in
their 70s to
90s
are crowded
around me
almost in
tears. The Red
Cross text get
me up on a
table, give me
a juice
and crackers,
and tell me to
lie there and
rest. The whole
time I'm kind's
laughing at how
stupid I
was. Long story
short, I
recovered, and
one of our
regular donors
walked me back
to my office to
eat something.
But poor Mrs.
Jody and Mrs.
June were
really upset.
They're the
sweetest
elderly
ladies and they
almost cried
when it
happened. And I
felt like a
total dick of
source wrecks
for
scaring them.
My mom chewed
me out. My
sibling who
lives half the
USA away chewed
me our.
My
gastroenterologist
read me the
absolute riot
act. In short,
I am really,
really dumb.
But my blood
saved a life in
Bacon County.
So, somebody
benefited.
TLDR gave blood
with a
condition that
causes blood
loss and nearly
scared two
sweet elderly
ladies half to
death when I
passed out and
hit my head.